Cameron Turner, my man.
卡梅隆特纳 伙计
Let me guess. Latte, oat milk, no sugar.
让我猜猜 拿铁、燕麦奶、不加糖
Spot on, sir.
没错 先生
I'll take an Echo bar if you've got any.
我要块爱可巧克力棒 如果你有的话
Echo's my middle name. Will that be all?
爱可我有得是 就这些吗？
That's good, thank you.
就这些 谢谢
All right. Payment taken. Order coming up.
好的 已收款 请稍候
Thank you, bro.
谢谢你 老弟
You're welcome, Cameron. Okay, good talk. We'll see you tomorrow.
不客气 卡梅隆 很高兴跟你聊 明天见
Step down from the train.
到站乘客请下车
Look, I know my brother, all right? He's very sensitive.
听着 我了解我哥哥 好吗？他很敏感
Hello?
喂？
Hey. Yeah.
嘿 是
No. We're pulling into the station now.
不 我们就要到站了
This station is Summit Park.
本站是山顶公园
I'll see you in a bit, okay? All right.
我们等会见 好吗？好的
Bye.
再见
It's all yours.
都归你
The train is now arriving at Summit Park.
列车到达山顶公园
The next station is Stadium Avenue.
下一站是体院场大道
Oh, my God.
天啊
Oh, fuck.
该死
Oh, no.
不
Oh, shit.
见鬼
I'm sorry. Excuse me.
对不起 抱歉
Cameron.
卡梅隆
Hi, Cameron. Dr. Scott here.
嗨 卡梅隆 我是斯科特医生
Look, I don't wanna add any more strain on you,
听着 我不想再给你更多压力
but with your latest scan showing an accelerating deterioration,
但是你最近的扫描显示情况在加速恶化
it's vital that we keep moving forward with--
所以至关重要的是我们要继续…
Mute.
静音
Pig. You out here?
小猪 你在外面吗？
Good boy, now.
好乖
You guys save me some food?
你们给我留饭了吗？
Yeah? You didn't eat all my food today?
是吗？你今天没把我的饭都吃掉？
Child prodigy or future serial killer?
神童还是未来的连环杀手？
Can't wait for parent-teacher night.
非常期待家长会之夜
Welcome to Arra House, Cameron. Good to meet you in person.
欢迎来到艾拉之家 卡梅隆 很高兴见到你本人
Come in.
请进
This is our main living area.
这是我们的主要生活区
Wow.
哇
I know that some of these concepts are uncomfortable.
我知道其中一些理念会让人不舒服
Just remember that if you decide not to proceed
只要记住如果你在评估过程中的任何时刻
at any point in the evaluation process, he never leaves this facility.
决定不再继续下去 他就永远不会离开这里
And there's-- there's no way he gets this thing?
那么…他绝对不会有我的病？
As outlined, we modified the relevant strands of his DNA
正如这里所列出的 我们调整了他的相关DNA链
to prevent that happening again.
以防止再发生这种情况
And what happens to him if I decide not to do this? He just--
如果我决定不进行 他会怎么样？他就…
He goes to sleep that night unaware. Doesn't know a thing.
他会在当天晚上毫不知情地睡去 什么都不会知道
We'll be calling him Jack for now, if that name's okay with you.
我们暂时称他为杰克 如果你同意这个名字
This is the control room.
这是控制室
And this is Dalton.
这是道尔顿
-Welcome, Cameron. -Hello.
-欢迎你 卡梅隆 -你好
He's a psychologist and the head technician.
他是一名心理学家 也是我们的首席技术员
And that completes our team.
这就是我们团队
It's just three of you?
只有你们三个人？
Three humans. Our AI systems do the work of about 50 people.
三个人类 我们的人工智能系统 承担大约50个人的工作
Before we let you in,
在我们让你进入之前
we'll need you to disable the cameras in your contacts and your watch.
我们需要你关掉 隐形眼镜和手表中的摄像头
Oh, okay.
好吧
Disable cameras.
关闭摄像头
Thank you.
谢谢
So, shall we go in?
那我们进去吧？
Molecularly regenerated.
通过分子再生创造
Mapped to your DNA.
与你的DNA完全相同
Cameron Turner to the molecule.
精确到分子的卡梅隆特纳
Is he dreaming?
他在做梦吗？
Not yet.
还没有
Go ahead. He can't wake.
请吧 他不会醒来
I'm sorry, Doctor.
我很抱歉 医生
I can't do this.
我不能这么做
I know what a momentous decision this is for you.
我理解这对你是一个多么重大的决定
I know what you're going through.
我知道你正在经历些什么
But just…
短信息 斯科特医生 在线 新闻 32分钟前更新 到达时间 20分钟后 我理解这对你是 一个多么重大的决定 我知道你正在经历些什么
the second you tell your wife that you're dying,
你一旦告诉你妻子你快死了 短信息 斯科特医生 在线 新闻 32分钟前更新 到达时间 20分钟后 我理解这对你是 一个多么重大的决定 我知道你正在经历些什么
your opportunity to do this is gone.
你做此事的机会就消失了
You can tell her,
你可以告诉她
or you can do this with us and let life go on for your family.
或者你可以跟我们合作 让你家人的生活继续下去
But given your worsening condition, we can't afford to delay, Cameron.
但鉴于你持续恶化的情况 我们拖延不起 卡梅隆
Please call me.
请给我回电
A surf scoter.
斑头海番鸭
Excellent. And this one?
好极了 那这个呢？
Cory?
科里？
Hooded mergant.
冠顶秋沙鸭
No.
不
Can I have your pencils?
能不能给我你的铅笔？
You eyeing my pencils now?
-你想要我的铅笔了？ -嗯哼
The same set I've had for 22 years. You're eyeing my pencils?
我用了22年的那套铅笔 你想要了？
You ain't using 'em.
反正你现在也没在使
"Ain't"? When did we start saying "ain't"?
“没在使”？ 我们什么时候开始这么说话了？
You don't use 'em since Andre died.
自从安德烈死了 你就不用了
Cam, what's with you lately?
卡梅 你最近是怎么回事？
Look, I know you're an artist and this is painful for you. I get it.
听着 我知道你是艺术家 这对你来说很痛苦 我明白
But this is a health-focused organic tea.
可这是一种注重健康的有机茶
It's not some fucking ayahuasca brew we're designing.
我们不是在设计什么该死的死藤水
When you follow along with what the client wants, you kill it, you know?
当你按照客户的要求去做 你会圆满完成任务 你明白吗？
So just play ball. Okay?
所以按照要求做就好 行吗？
-All right. -Love ya. Bye.
-好吧 -爱你 再见
You want one of these?
你想吃吗？
-Uncle Andre. -Cory, can you say "Uncle Andre"?
-安德烈舅舅 -科里 说“安德烈舅舅”？
That is cloning, by the way.
顺便一提 那就是克隆
-No! -Yeah.
-不 -是的
No, technically speaking, it's not. The article said it's not.
不 严格来说 那不是 文章说那不是
It's-- It's regeneration.
是…再生
It doesn't matter what you call it, Andre. It's still weird.
不管你叫它什么 安德烈 那还是怪怪的
I don't care how good they say the tech's gonna be.
我不管他们说那项技术有多么先进
You'd know it wasn't a real person in seconds.
你会立刻知道那不是一个真人
Look, I'm just saying, hypothetically speaking,
听着 我只是说 从理论上来说
what if it was actually possible? What if they did actually work it out?
如果那真的可能呢？ 如果他们真的研究出来了呢？
They won't, Andre. 'Cause you can't copy a human being. You can't.
不可能 安德烈 因为你无法复制一个人 你做不到
-Cameron? -No. I-- No, I'm staying way out of this.
-卡梅隆 -不 我不…参与这个对话
Oh, come on.
少来
Nothing like a good death chat first thing in the morning.
再没有比一大早讨论死亡更丧的了
Okay.
好吧
-Is that funny? -Right? It's ridiculous. Come on.
-好笑是吗？ -对吗？太可笑了
Look, if Mom could be sitting here right now with us,
听着 如果妈妈可以现在 跟我们在这里坐在一起
and, like, you know, we couldn't tell, she was indistinguishable, then yeah.
我们看不出来 她完全一模一样 那我就同意
You know, screw the ethics. I would take that.
去他的伦理道德吧 我可以接受
I mean, that being said,
尽管这么说
if they happen to delete her fondness for yacht rock,
如果他们碰巧删除了她对游艇摇滚的喜爱
-I would not be devastated. -Yes.
-我不会伤心欲绝 -对
Going crazy. Gimme the lips, Poppy. Gimme the lips.
太疯狂了 学学她的嘴唇 波比 学学她的嘴唇
There it is.
就是这样
Yes.
是的
I know how you're feeling, but there is no lie.
我理解你的感受 但这里不存在谎言
When the memory of this process gets wiped,
当关于这个过程的记忆被抹去
he wakes up that day at home as Cameron Turner.
他会在那一天作为卡梅隆特纳在家里醒来
And no one knows. Not even him.
没有人知道 连他自己都不知道
It's the only way this works. A clean swap.
这是唯一奏效的办法 干净彻底的交换
How many others are out there? I wanna know.
还有多少其他的人？我想知道
You'll be our third.
你是我们的第三个
This will be as common as a heart transplant within a few years.
在几年之内 这将会像心脏移植手术一样平常
Come back and spend a week with him before making your decision.
回来和他共处一周 然后你再做决定
This is not just my decision. My wife needs to know.
这不仅仅是我的决定 我妻子必须知道
Either you decide that your wife would want this, which requires secrecy,
要么你决定这是你妻子所希望的 那就必须保密
or you decide that she wouldn't, and tell her you're dying.
要么你决定她不希望这样 那就告诉她你快死了
Either way, you're deciding for her.
无论如何 是你在为她做决定
Listen, the woman you're about to meet has no idea she's a duplicate.
听着 你将见到的女人 根本不知道她是克隆人
Neither does her daughter, her mother, or her friends.
她的女儿、母亲或朋友都不知道
So, where is the lie?
那么有什么谎言可言呢？
Oh, hey, there. Mr. Turner, right?
你好 你是特纳先生 对吗？
Yeah, uh, Cameron.
是 卡梅隆
Browsing for a three-bed in the neighborhood?
想在这个区找三间卧室的房子？
Oh, yeah.
是的
This is, uh, my boss, Samantha.
这是我的老板 萨曼莎
I'm her daughter.
我是她女儿
Daughter.
女儿
She runs a tight ship.
她是个严厉的老板
Anyway, have a seat.
总之 请坐吧
I had some good ones come in today, actually.
正好我今天拿到一些好房子
You said in your message you had a son, right?
你给我的信息里说你有一个儿子 对吗？
Yeah. Cory.
是的 科里
He runs the show as well?
他也是你家的老板？
Yeah. The smaller, the bossier.
对 年龄越小脾气越大
-Hey. -Hey.
-嘿-嘿
-Yeah? -Yeah.
-怎么样？ -很好
Cory at Jessie's for dinner?
科里在杰西家吃晚饭？
Yeah. He's back at 8:00.
对 他8点回来
-You taking a break? -Yeah.
-你在休息吗？ -是
So I think we're gonna get Dr. Herbert for the ultrasound.
我想我们会让赫伯特医生做超声波检查
I'm just waiting for them to confirm, but it's looking good.
我在等他们确认 不过很有希望
Yeah.
是
That's good. We like Herbert.
太好了 我们喜欢赫伯特
Are you bracing yourself for sexy bowling ball bod?
你准备好面对性感的保龄球肚皮了吗？
I still can't believe it.
我还是不敢相信
We're gonna fall in love with a new little person again.
我们又要爱上一个小家伙了
Seven months.
七个月
What's up, Cam?
怎么了 卡梅？
I'm good. It's just, um…
我没事 只是…
It's just, um…
只是…
So, we, um…
那么我们…
Cameron?
卡梅隆？
It's just, a new little person. And…
只是 一个新的小生命…
I think that's just sinking in still, you know.
我想我还在适应当中
Oh, bear.
熊熊
Cam.
卡梅
I know it took me a minute,
我知道我用了很长时间
and I know we haven't been us for a while,
我也知道我们的关系最近不太和谐
but this baby is going to be good for us.
但这个宝宝会对我们有好处
Yeah.
是啊
We're gonna be okay. All right?
我们会没事的 好吗？
Cory.
科里
Cameron?
卡梅隆
I've changed my mind.
我改变主意了
Mind if I sit?
我可以坐下吗？
Hi. I'm Cameron.
嗨 我是…卡梅隆
Kate.
凯特
So, you met her?
你见到她了？
Yesterday.
昨天
How's she doing?
她怎么样？
Good. I guess.
挺好的 大概吧
She try to sell you a house?
她想卖房子给你？
Condo.
康斗
It's what we do.
那是我们的工作
A week?
一周？
And the clients just spring this on you today, zero notice?
客户今天突然这样要求 根本没有提前通知？
What's going on, Cam?
卡梅 发生什么事了？
Nothing.
没事
The designer they had got sick last minute and they needed someone here in person.
他们的设计师突然病倒 他们需要一个人在现场
Look, I'm sorry, P. I am.
听着 我很抱歉 波 真的
I wish I didn't have to be away right now. Believe me.
我真希望我现在不必离开你 相信我
All right. Well, I'd better get back here.
好吧 我得过去了
-I'll speak to you later, yeah? -All right.
-我们回头再聊 好吗？ -好的
Okay, Cameron.
好吧 卡梅隆
You'll be out for the entire process. It'll take about six hours.
整个过程中你都会无知觉 大约需要六个小时
Okay. He'll have everything?
好吧 他什么都会有？
Every single memory
全部的记忆
right up to the moment you lose consciousness in that chair.
一直到你在那把椅子中失去知觉的那一刻
In a few moments, you're gonna go under.
几秒钟之后你就会失去知觉
Okay. I think I--
好的 我想我…
I thi--
我…
Like, you having a moment. You having a day.
你享受这一刻 你享受这一天
Thank you.
谢谢
So, he has everything?
那么他全都有了？
Even the memories you've stored deep in your subconscious.
甚至包括你深藏在潜意识中的记忆
All those memories, they're not just mine.
所有那些记忆 它们不仅是我的
They're my wife's, my son's.
它们也是我…妻子的、我儿子的
Not part of some experiment.
而不是什么实验的一部分
I just wish I could talk to her.
我真希望我能跟她谈谈
When they sent "me 2.0" back,
当他们把我的2.0版本送回去
seeing my mom look into her eyes not knowing it wasn't me,
看到我妈妈注视着她的眼睛 不知道那不是我
seeing her talking to my daughter…
看到她跟我女儿说话
I mean…
我是说…
And then when they wiped her…
然后当他们抹去她的记忆
knowing she was no longer in on the lie, my guilt faded pretty quick.
知道她不再是这个谎言的参与者 我的内疚感很快就消失了
We share an oncologist, you know?
我们有同一个肿瘤医生 你知道吗？
Dr. Kerosima?
克罗西马医生？
Yep.
对
The patient before me was a patient of hers too.
我之前的病人也是她的病人
She seemed happy, your daughter. They both did.
她看起来很快乐 你女儿 她们都很快乐
Yeah?
是吗？
How long has she been out there?
她在外面多久了？
Roughly…
大约…
forty-two days, six hours.
42天零6小时
Roughly?
大约？
Ballpark.
差不多吧
Memory cross-checks allow us to make sure
记忆对照检查让我们能够确认
that his conscious and subconscious memories
他的意识内和潜意识内的记忆
are perfectly in sync with yours.
完全符合你的记忆
It will feel strange at first.
开始可能感觉有些奇怪
Just try to stay in each memory.
你只要努力停留在每个记忆中
In your own time, Cameron.
你什么时候开始都行 卡梅隆
Hi.
嗨
Cameron, I like your picture.
卡梅隆 我喜欢你的画
Breathe.
呼吸
It feels real because as far as your brain is concerned, it is real.
这感觉真实 因为对你的大脑而言 它就是真的
Just, skipped way back.
只是倒回去了好多年
That's normal.
这很正常
As it progresses, the system will test any point in time
随着系统的进步 它会测试任何时间点
all the way back to birth.
一直回到出生的时候
It's vital that you do your best to stay in the memories
你需要努力停留在记忆中 这非常重要
and not break the flow, okay?
不要打断过程 好吗？
Okay.
好的
When you're good.
你准备好就开始
Hi, remember me from a few weeks back?
嗨 还记得我吗？ 几周前我们见过
Yeah. You ate my chocolate bar.
是的 你吃了我的巧克力棒
See, I also purchased an Echo bar.
是这样 我也买了一个爱可巧克力棒
And I'm hoping you worked that out by now. Yeah.
我…希望你现在已经搞明白了
Yeah. I'd have loved to see your face when you realized.
我真希望看到你意识到时脸上的表情
Not a strong moment for me.
不是我的荣耀时刻
I just saw you, um, just sitting here,
我刚看见你坐在那里
and I-- I made this thing.
我就…画了这个
It's in my bag.
在我包里
Here you go.
给你
Wow! Wow, you're good.
哇 你画得真好
Oh, thank you. I realize now
谢谢 我现在意识到
that even makes me look more like a psycho.
这让我更像一个神经病了
-Oh, yeah? -But I'm not! I'm not. I promise.
-噢 是吗？ -不过我不是…我保证
A talented psycho is better than a talentless one, so…
有才华的神经病 比没才华的神经病强 所以…
Yeah. I appreciate that.
是啊 谢谢你这么说
I'm Cameron, by the way.
对了 我…叫卡梅隆
Cameron. Poppy.
卡梅隆 我叫波比
Poppy.
波比
Pleasure.
幸会
My stop's coming up.
我要到站了
Oh, okay. Um, all right. Well, I'll let you go.
好的 好吧 那就再见吧
Sorry again for eating your candy bar.
很抱歉我吃了你的巧克力棒
I hope to see you around.
我希望回头再碰见你
-The next station is Summit Park. -All right, best wishes.
-下一站是山顶公园 -好吧 万事如意
Best wishes.
万事如意
Hey, Cameron?
嘿 卡梅隆
Here.
给你
Oh, no, that's for you. Keep it.
不 那是给你的 留着吧
Give it to me again.
你下次再给我
Okay.
好吧
Poppy.
波比
-Yeah? Are you scared yet? -I'm a little bit scared.
-怎么样？害怕了吗？ -有一点害怕
Like, there's a lot going on there.
画里的内容很丰富的
You mean that awful thing I made the other day?
你是说那天我做的那个糟糕的东西吗？
Yes!
好
Let me out.
让我出来
You hold on a little bit. I'm not ready for you.
你再等等 我还没准备好迎接你
We've been waiting so long for you.
我们等你很久了
She reminds me so much of Cory. You're so sweet.
她让我想起科里 你好乖
And then there was a third one.
然后有第三个
I don't wanna look at you. It makes me laugh.
我不想看你 那让我发笑
Mommy.
妈妈
-I'm not going back in. -It's okay.
-我不回去 -没事的
I saw her upstairs in her room,
我看见她在楼上她的房间里
and she was crying, and she looked really sad.
她在哭泣 她看起来很伤心
Is it because of Andre?
是因为安德烈吗？
Cameron Turner, my twin brother, Andre.
卡梅隆特纳 这是我的双胞胎兄弟 安德烈
Hey, Andre.
嗨 安德烈
-I should have stopped him. -No, no, no, no.
-我本应该阻止他 -不…
I should have stopped him.
我本该阻止他
It's my fault, Cam. It's my fault.
都怪我 卡梅 都怪我
-I-- -You good, Cameron?
-我… -卡梅隆 你没事吧？
-I'm sorry. I need a second. -All right.
-对不起 给我一分钟 -好吧
All right. Let's go.
好吧 我们继续
You're booking days off now?
你现在安排休假了？
Yeah, I booked time off so we can hang out when I get back.
对 我安排了休假 这样等我回来 我们就可以共度时光
I've been trying to peel you away from your desk for the last six months.
这过去的六个月 我一直试图把你从办公桌前拉开
Suddenly you're gung-ho to drop everything.
突然你就要毅然决然地放下一切
I know. You're right. It's--
我知道 你说得对 是…
Bear?
熊熊？
-You good? -Yeah. Yes.
-你没事吧？ -没事
Yeah?
是吗？
Are you sure you're happy about this?
你确定你对这件事开心吗？
Yeah. The last couple of weeks you just…
过去这两周你…
I don't know. Just--
我不知道 只是…
Hey, P. I'm fine. It's just work. I'm working.
嘿 波 我没事 都是因为工作 我在工作
I… I just hate being away from you. That's all.
我…只是不喜欢离开你而已
And I just miss us.
我很想念我们
When I get home, we're gonna hang out and talk for real, okay?
等我回到家 我们好好谈谈 好吗？
Okay, Cameron.
好的 卡梅隆
Oh, my God.
我的天
Okay, you're definitely taking the blame for this specimen.
好吧 这件东西一定是你的错
No. I believe Cory picked that out himself.
不 我相信是科里自己挑的
-What? At three months? -Yeah. Because I was with him.
-什么？在三个月大的时候？ -是的 因为我跟他在一起
We were in the store walking around,
我们在商店里转悠
and I'm pushing him in the stroller. And he's like, "Hey. Yo, big man.
我推着坐在婴儿车里的他 他说：“嘿 你 老大
You see that yellow mustard onesie right there?
你看见那件芥末黄的连身衣了吗？
I need that in my life."
我的人生需要它”
Yeah, he's so charming. I was like, "Hey, what do you say to that?"
是啊 他那么有魅力 我说“嘿 你觉得怎么样？”
Yeah, he is very charming. I'll give you that.
对 他是很有魅力 这个我同意
But this is criminal.
可是这简直是犯罪
Together, me and you will take care of her
你和我一起照顾她
till she can take care of herself again. All right?
直到她可以自己照顾自己 好吗？
Me and you gotta be strong for her, okay? She's just sick right now.
我们俩都得为了她坚强一些 好吗？ 她现在只是生病了
Go away.
走开
Wake up, man. Come on.
醒来吧 小子 快点
At least six more hours.
至少再睡六个小时
Six more hours?
再睡六个小时？
It's still dark outside. Look!
外面天还黑着呢 看
'Cause it's early. But you gotta wake up, man. We gotta go.
因为天还早 可是你得醒来了 孩子 我们得走了
Let this hand go. There, boom.
放开这只手 对了 轰
-And now flick it. Follow through. -Boom.
-现在转动手腕 随球动作 -进了
I used to do this all day in my room.
我曾经整天在我房间里玩这个
-That smells so good. -You think?
-真好闻 -是吗？
-Kale. Kale. Kale. Mint. And mint. -Yes. All right.
-羽衣甘蓝…薄荷… -是的 对了
Dip 'em in a little-- a little soy sauce.
把它蘸…一点酱油
Okay. I'm standing by up here.
好了 我在这里待命
How long will it take?
需要多长时间？
He should wake instantly.
他应该马上醒来
Okay. We're ready to go up here.
好的 我们这里准备好了
All right.
好吧
Okay.
好
Keep your eyes closed.
闭着你的眼睛
I'm gonna count you down from three.
我给你从三开始倒数
And on three…
三…
And two…
二…
And one.
一
You're okay.
你没事
Breathe.
呼吸
-That's it? -That's it.
-就是这样？ -就是这样
Everything go okay?
一切顺利？
Everything went great.
一切非常顺利
When will I see him?
我什么时候能见他？
In the morning.
明天早上
Until then, you should get some sleep.
在那之前 你应该好好睡一觉
For the time that you are in this facility,
你在这里的这段时间
that freckle is the only place on your entire body
这个斑点是你全身
that isn't identical to his.
唯一跟他不同的地方
If you get confused,
如果你弄混了
you find that freckle and you'll know who you are. Okay?
你找到那个斑点 就知道自己是谁了 好吗？
We know how strange this is.
我们理解这种感觉多么奇怪
You got the good deal here.
你这样做非常合算
You'll see.
你会明白的
Boom! Again.
砰 再来
-Little chin music. -You're going down.
-来点下巴音乐 -你要输了
You don't know nothing about this, boy.
你根本不懂 孩子
You too young.
你太年轻
Chump.
没门 傻小子
Yeah!
好耶
Boom!
砰
-Yeah, baby! -That's just another cheap left.
-太棒了 -又一个偷偷摸摸的左勾拳
End call.
结束通话
Dad?
爸爸？
-Hey, Cameron? -Talk to me, Cameron.
-嘿 卡梅隆 -说话呀 卡梅隆
-No. -Send Poppy a message.
-不 -给波比发信息
They're saying any of these seizures could kill me.
他们说我会死于任何一次癫痫发作
And I could die out here this week before getting home to see them.
在回去看他们之前 我有可能这周就死在这里
I can't stop picturing her getting the news, having to tell Cory.
我无法停止想象她得到消息 不得不告诉科里
Poppy and I had been going through some stuff.
波比和我经历了一些事情
The other night I made her laugh.
那天晚上我让她笑了
I can't remember the last time I did that, you know?
我不记得上次让她笑是什么时候 你懂吗？
Just made her laugh.
让她发笑
That's because you're not funny.
那是因为你不风趣
Yeah, that too.
对 那也是原因
Those things will kill you, you know.
那种东西会致死
Oh, you are funny. Fuck that.
你其实挺风趣的 去他的
Cameron?
卡梅隆
We're ready for you.
我们一切就绪了
See you later.
回头见
Have fun.
玩得开心
Poppy's the world's best sleeper.
波比是世界上最能睡的人
When she's tired, she'll just drift off in seconds,
她累了的时候 几秒钟之内就能睡着
like, out like a light.
就像灯一下子灭了
Poppy speaks French?
波比会说法语？
Yeah, she'll still say the occasional French word.
她依旧偶尔说些法语词
Like, she'll say…
比如 她会说 “晚安”
Or…
或者…
Or if something is great, like, just perfect,
如果什么事情很棒 非常完美
she might whisper…
她可能会小声说…
You wanna go say hi?
你想去打个招呼吗？
You okay?
你好吗？
After last night?
昨晚之后？
Good.
挺好的
I don't know how to…
我不知道如何…
What to say here.
说什么
I know you don't think I'm…
我知道你不认为我…
You.
是你…
I'm sitting up in that room, looking at Rafa.
我坐在那个房间看着拉法
My heart is beating out of my chest, and, um, I'm nervous.
我的心脏剧烈跳动 我很紧张
I'm really nervous.
我真的很紧张
Then Dad pops in my head.
然后爸爸突然出现在我脑海里
That first trip out to see him after they split.
他们离婚后 第一次去看他
Getting on that airplane.
登上那驾飞机
Just the nerves, you know?
紧张得要命 你知道吗？
And I close my eyes.
我闭上眼
And then I open 'em.
然后睁开
I'm not up there in that room anymore.
我不在那个房间里了
I'm here.
我在这里
I am here.
我就在这里
I'm sorry, man. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
我很抱歉 伙计 我很抱歉…
He knows you're nervous, Jack.
他知道你很紧张 杰克
Just answer the questions.
只要回答问题就好
-Audio muted. -Cameron…
-关闭音频 -卡梅隆
you're you.
你就是你
There are no wrong answers.
不存在错误的答案
Audio unmuted.
音频恢复
Okay, Jack. Poppy works with children.
好的 杰克 波比从事儿童工作
Yeah, she teaches kids with learning difficulties
对 她教有学习困难的儿童
through music therapy.
通过音乐疗法
She's got her own take on the Orff Schulwerk method.
她对奥尔夫舒维克教学法有独特的见解
So, um, she makes songs with the kids, and she puts them in the songs.
她和孩子们创作音乐 把他们放到歌曲中
And… they love it.
他们很喜欢
She's just insanely talented.
她就是才华横溢
She cares. You know? Like, she really cares.
她在乎 你知道吗？她真的很在乎
Did you always want children?
你一直都想要孩子吗？
I like this, Cameron Turner.
我喜欢这个 卡梅隆特纳
I think after I met Poppy, I realized I wanted kids.
我想我是在认识波比后 意识到自己想要孩子
I like all of this.
这些我都喜欢
Yeah.
是
I was cynical for a long time.
我愤世嫉俗了很长时间
Wow. Oh, my gosh.
哇 天啊
We have scarily similar taste in books.
我们对书的品味相似得令人害怕
This idea of finding true love or a soul mate.
找到真爱或心灵伴侣的想法
Then someone like Poppy comes along and you realize you're just surviving.
然后像波比这样的人突然出现 你意识到你只是在生存
Do you play?
你演奏音乐吗？
I butcher.
我乱弹一气
But I'm not playing in front of you.
不过我可不要在你面前演奏
I could have just gone on like that forever.
我本来会就那样混下去
You better stop And think about what you doing
你最好停下 想想你在做什么
Oh, I love it. Yes.
我喜欢 好
I just lucked out, I guess.
我想我实在太幸运了
Good.
很好
Talk about your parents' relationship.
说说你父母的关系
Well, there's not really much to talk about.
其实没什么可说的
They divorced when I was five, and my dad moved away for work.
我五岁的时候他们离婚了 我爸爸因为工作原因搬家了
He was a doctor. A pediatrician.
他是个医生 儿科医生…
He looks like me. He sounds like me, but I don't know…
他看起来像我、声音像我 可我不知道…
In seven months, that child is gonna come into the world without a dad.
七个月之后 那个孩子就会来到世上 没有爸爸
Seven months.
七个月
Hey. At least you're not feeling sorry for yourself.
嘿 至少你不为自己难过
Oh, okay. That's fair.
好吧 这很公平
You're gonna be good, man.
你会没事的 伙计
That's fair.
这很公平
And what about you? How you doing?
那你呢？你怎么样？
Me?
我？
Never better.
从来没这么好过
Any other great questions?
还有别的好问题吗？
No. Okay.
没有 好吧
Yep.
对
Having the time of my life out here.
在这里我真是开心极了
Nature's awesome. Great food.
美丽的大自然 美味的食物
Cameron?
卡梅隆
Make it obscure.
说一个隐晦的
Andre. Gift.
安德烈 礼物
Am I actually gonna like this?
我会喜欢吗？
-Probably not. It's probably-- -Oh, God. What?
-大概不会 也许… -天啊 什么？
-Lift your feet up high. -Lift my feet up where?
-把脚抬高 -把脚抬到哪？
-And step. Step. Step. -Whoa! Oops. Oh, no! No! Oh.
-走… -不行 不…
There we go. There you go.
对了…
We're safe. We're safe.
很安全…
What is it?
是什么啊？
You got me a piano!
你送我一台钢琴
Andre!
安德烈
Oh, my God.
天啊
-Thank you so much. -And he was so like Poppy.
-太谢谢你了 -他跟波比太像了
Like, just wildly smart and gentle.
超级聪明 人又温柔
What happened to him?
他出了什么事？
Andre… was thrown from his bike off of a mountain road.
安德烈在一条山路上行驶时 从摩托车上摔下
His body landed in the branches of a pine tree, high up.
他的身体落在一棵很高的松树上
Every couple of weeks, I dream about him up there in the treetops.
每隔几周我都会梦见他在树梢上
Alone. Just laying there.
独自一人躺在那里
Have you talked to your wife about that dream?
你跟你妻子谈过那个梦吗？
No.
没有
Why not?
为什么没有？
She didn't leave the house for the better part of a year.
那一年她有一大半时间都没出门
Slept in the guest room most of that time, so…
大部分时间睡在客房
I'm just trying to help you.
我只想帮你
I know, I know.
我知道…
-I need to be alone. Thank you. -Please--
-我需要独自待着 谢谢 -拜托…
It's not really subject matter we enjoy getting into.
那不是我们想要提起的话题
How did Poppy sleeping apart make you feel?
波比睡在别处让你有何感受？
Alone.
孤独
Mostly, I worried about her.
主要是我担心她
I missed her.
我想念她
Did you resent her for it?
你有没有为此怨恨她？
She lost her twin.
她失去了双胞胎兄弟
She never felt good about him getting that motorcycle.
她一直对他买那辆摩托车感到不安
Blamed herself for not protesting more.
责怪自己没有更强烈地反对
But he was gonna get the bike anyway.
可是他无论如何是要买那辆摩托车的
You've mentioned how well Poppy has progressed with her therapist
你说过波比在治疗师的帮助下取得了很大进展
over the last few months.
就在过去的这几个月
But you never went to see anybody?
但你从来没有找过治疗师？
No.
没有
Did you talk to someone after your parents were divorced?
在你父母离婚后 你跟任何人谈过吗？
No, I was five.
没有 我当时才五岁
So you've never been to a therapist?
那么你从来没有看过心理治疗师？
No.
没有
And you can't talk to Poppy about this dream that you keep having?
你不能告诉波比这个你反复做的梦？
It's been two years. Why haven't you gone to see somebody?
已经两年了 为什么你没有去看过治疗师？
I don't know.
我不知道
Cameron?
卡梅隆
I'm sorry, I--
抱歉 我…
I'm sorry.
我很抱歉
It's okay.
没关系
Let's take a break.
我们休息一下
Saving them for you.
给你留的
All right.
好了
Jack, are you ready?
杰克 你准备好了吗？
-Cameron? -Yeah.
-卡梅隆呢？ -好了
All right.
好吧
Call Poppy, please.
请给波比打电话
This is weird timing. I just spoke to the clinic.
这也太凑巧了吧 我刚跟诊所通了话
Doctor Herbert is confirmed for the ultrasound on the 25th.
已经确认了赫伯特医生 在25号给我做超声波检查
Cam?
卡梅？
That's real.
这太真实了
Yeah. So real. Living human in body.
是啊 很真实 身体里有个小生命
Just feels so different to how I remember it with Cory, right?
感觉和我记忆中科里那次完全不同 对吗？
Yeah.
是啊
Remember how we found out?
你记得我们是怎么知道的吗？
Oh, my God, yeah. That insane snow.
天啊 是啊 那场大雪
Jessie and Zoe's wedding the next day.
第二天是杰西和柔伊的婚礼
Zoe knew right away.
柔伊马上就知道了
"Oh, my God. You're pregnant, Poppy."
“天啊 你怀孕了 波比”
Oh, I remember that feeling.
我记得那种感觉
You were barely out of the doctor's office,
你还没走出医生办公室
you were already making a playlist, holding the speaker there.
就已经在制作播放列表 把音箱放在这里
Yeah. Yes. Womb tunes.
是啊 对 子宫音乐
Womb tunes. Oh, it's been a minute.
子宫音乐 那是好久以前了
Hey, we should tell Cory soon, too.
嘿 我们也应该尽快告诉科里
Yeah, I was thinking the same--
对 我也这么想…
Rafa, send Poppy a message.
拉法 给波比发条信息
-What did you do? -I don't like this.
-你做什么？ -我不喜欢这样
And you think I like this? Talking to my wife under a spotlight?
你以为我喜欢吗？ 在聚光灯下跟我的妻子说话？
She's not your wife!
她不是你的妻子
Oh, okay. Okay, I see.
好吧…我明白了
You can't bear to see this actually work. That's the real problem.
你受不了看到这实际上是奏效的 这才是真正的问题
-Fuck you, man! -Fuck you!
-去死吧 -你去死
And what about me? Waking up in this place,
我怎么了？在这里地方醒来
waiting for you to pull the plug, being told I'm not me.
等着你拔掉电源 被告知我不是我
Because you're not me.
因为你不是我
You are not me!
你不是我
You know what? Fuck all this.
算了 让这见鬼去吧
-No, bullshit. You stay right here. -This is bullshit! Fuck that!
-不 狗屁 你哪也别去 -这是狗屁 见鬼去吧
-Stay here. Bullshit. This is real. -Open the fucking door!
-你别走 少来 这是真的 -打开门
And you know it. You know it.
你知道的…
Poppy said if she couldn't tell, if her mom was indistinguishable…
波比说如果她看不出来 如果她的妈妈没有任何区别…
Well, here it is. Indistinguishable.
这就是了 没有任何区别
You won't go through with it because you're too selfish!
你不想做这件事 因为你太自私
Get the fuck off me.
别碰我
I'm done with you. Huh?
我不想看见你了
Do something? Do it. Fuck you, do it. Do it!
想做吗？做吧 你去死 做吧…
Yeah. You won't leave this place.
对 你不会离开这里的
I'm going home, and I'm telling them everything. Everything!
我会回家去 我会告诉他们所有事 所有事
Yeah, I bet you will. Bitch ass.
好呀 我打赌你会的 王八蛋
It's always about you. It's always about you.
你一直只关心自己…
She's been trying to talk for I don't know how long,
她一直想跟你谈 我都不知道多久了
and you keep shutting her out,
你一直在躲避她
because deep down inside, you feel like she abandoned us.
因为在你内心深处 你觉得她抛弃了我们
-I never thought that! I never! -You did!
-我从来没那么想 从来没有 -你就是这么想
You did--
你就是…
Hey, hey. Hey.
嘿…
It's okay. It's okay. Breathe, breathe.
没事…呼吸…
Cam?
卡梅
What the fuck, man?
怎么搞的？
He shouldn't go home in that state.
他这种情况不应该回去
I'll talk to him, but it's in his contract.
我会跟他谈 但他的合同里有这条
I need to see him.
我要见他
I remember when I knew she was gonna be okay.
我记得当我知道她会没事的那一刻
I used to cry for Tracy
我曾为特雷西哭泣
I wanted to see him again
我想再次见到他
But sometimes Sometimes life ain't always the way
但有时候 生活并不是这样
Sometimes it snows in April
有时4月会下雪
Sometimes I feel so bad
有时我感觉如此难过
So bad
如此难过
Sometimes I wish life is never-ending
有时我希望生命永不终止
And all good things They say never last
他们说好景不常在 好花不常开
And love
还有爱
It isn't hard till it's passed
直到逝去 才知艰辛
Hey, uh… I'm really sorry about earlier.
嘿…对刚才的事 我很抱歉
I don't think she abandoned us.
我不认为她抛弃了我们
No, there's something to it.
不 你说的有点道理
There's something to it.
有点道理
She'd been trying to talk to me for a long time in her own way.
很久以来她一直想跟我谈 以她自己的方式
Thought I had more time, I guess.
我以为还有时间
I just told her about that dizzy spell three months ago.
三个月前我才告诉她我头晕的事
If I'd had mentioned the headache back then--
如果我那时告诉她我头痛…
She'd have marched us in for a scan that day.
她一定会当天让我去医院做扫描
And got to it before it spread.
在扩散之前进行治疗
Dealt with it together.
共同面对
I know you got to go back and see them. I get it.
我知道你必须回去看他们 我理解
Do the right thing here.
做正确的事
In seven months, that baby--
七个月后 那个孩子…
Don't do that.
别这样
If you tell her, you're saying it for you. I'm saying that for them.
如果你告诉她 你是为了自己这样做 我在替他们着想
Enough.
够了
Morning.
早上好
Hey, Jack.
嘿 杰克
Hey, hey. You're okay. It's okay.
嘿…你没事…
-Oh, shit. -You're okay.
-该死 -你没事
You're okay.
你没事
Yeah.
是
Monitoring your lens feed while you're back at home
你在家期间 监控你的隐形眼镜信号流
is an important part of Jack's psychological evaluation.
是对杰克进行心理评估的重要部分
Nothing's ever recorded?
不会录制任何内容？
That's the policy.
这是我们的政策
And only Jack has access to this feed?
只有杰克才能看信号流？
No one sees or hears a thing.
没有人能看到或听到任何信号
Access granted.
授予访问权限
Now, try your best to forget about all this,
现在尽量忘记这一切
and just enjoy your time with them.
好好享受和他们在一起的时光
We'll see you in three days, Cameron.
我们三天后见 卡梅隆
Try to put everything out of your mind. Just enjoy your time at home.
尽量把一切都抛在脑后 享受在家的时光吧
Do come back.
请一定回来
Oh, my God.
天啊
Call him. Send a car.
打电话给他 派辆车去
Pick up.
站起来
Cameron, there will be a car there in a moment. Try to stand up.
卡梅隆 汽车马上就到 尝试站起来
Cameron?
卡梅隆？
We're gonna need you to come back.
我们需要你回来
I just got home.
我刚到家
We might just need to change your medication,
我们可能只需要改变你的药物
but we gotta have a look at you.
但是我们必须对你进行检查
I'm not going back.
我不回去
If you stay and you have another seizure without supervision,
如果你留在那里 在没有人监督的情况下 发生一次癫痫发作
you could die in front of your family.
你可能死在你家人的面前
Fuck you.
去死吧
Fuck. Fuck.
去死吧…
Cameron?
卡梅隆？
Cameron, talk to me.
卡梅隆 跟我讲话
Jack goes in the morning.
杰克明早去
I haven't finished evaluating his psychological state yet.
我还没有完成对他的心理状态评估
I'm not comfortable with Jack going home.
我对杰克回家感到不放心
Poppy's expecting him back.
波比在等他回去
-I have-- -Jack is ready. He goes first thing.
-我已经… -杰克准备好了 他明天一早就去
We're covered for this in the contract.
合同里规定我们可以这么做
It will be noted that you opposed the decision.
将注明你反对这个决定
Tell Jack to call Poppy now.
让杰克现在给波比打电话
You slipped in the shower. Mild concussion. Scan was all good.
你在浴室滑倒了 轻微脑震荡 扫描显示没问题
Home tomorrow.
明天到家
All right.
好吧
If these two weeks at home go well, which they will,
如果这两周在家里一切顺利 肯定会的
your memory of this process will be removed
你关于这个过程的记忆会被抹去
and we will not see you here again.
我们再也不会在这里见到你了
If Cameron wakes up, he will monitor your lens feed.
如果卡梅隆醒来 他会监控你的隐形眼镜信号流
But unless there are any issues over the next two weeks,
除非在接下来的两周有任何问题
he will not have the option to stop this.
否则他没有权力停止
I know this isn't as we planned it, but you're ready, Jack.
我知道这和我们的计划不同 不过你准备好了 杰克
Don't think of these two weeks as a test.
不要把这两周当成是考验
Just going home.
只是回家而已
Bear? Let me see you.
熊熊？让我看看你
Are you okay?
你没事吧？
-Just-- Just a little bit sore. I'm fine. -Yeah?
-只是…有点痛 我很好 -是吗？
The swelling's gone down.
肿块已经退去了
What did they say?
他们说什么？
I'll be a little bit fuzzy for a few days. But I'm good.
接下来的几天我会有点头晕 不过我没事
Come here.
过来
You scared me.
你吓坏我了
I scared me.
我被自己吓坏了
He's waiting for you up in his room.
他在他房间等你
-Who? -Your son.
-谁？ -你儿子
Shut up.
闭嘴
Asshole.
混蛋
I'm sorry, I had to.
抱歉 我没忍住
Shit, Cam. Don't freak me out like that.
该死 卡梅 别那样吓我
Wanker.
混蛋
-Come here. -No.
-过来 -不
Come here.
过来
-No way. -I'm sorry.
-不要 -对不起
Easy, tiger.
放松点
Pig.
小猪
What the hell? Ellington?
怎么回事？艾灵顿
Hey, pal.
嘿 伙计
Wow, I think Pig's pissed at you
我想小猪很生你的气
for leaving town and hitting your head.
因为你出差还撞到了头
Wow, he is not letting it go. Ellington.
它真是不依不饶的 艾灵顿
Okay, Pig.
好了 小猪
I'll stick him outside.
我把它放到外面去
I'll go check on Doc.
我去看看小博士
Hey.
嘿
Ra-- What happened?
拉…发生什么了？
You passed out.
你昏倒了
You've been unconscious for almost 24 hours.
你失去知觉几乎24小时了
What does Poppy think?
波比会怎么想？
Everything's fine, Cameron.
一切都很好 卡梅隆
What does that mean?
你这是什么意思？
He's not gone.
他没去吧
We've been monitoring it all while you were out. Everything's good.
在你昏迷的时候 我们在监控一切 一切都很顺利
No. No, no, no. I didn't get--
不…我没有…
I'm so sorry that it happened this way…
我很抱歉事情发生了变化…
I'm not done. I didn't say he could go.
我还没做完 我没说他可以去
-…but it was the right decision. -Bullshit.
-但这是正确的决定 -狗屁
I'm not done!
我还没做完
Well, it's not about you now.
现在这不是你一个人的事了
Excuse me?
你说什么？
-You have an opportunity that no one gets. -No. No, no, no.
-你现在有个任何人都不会有的机会 -不…
Don't be blind, Cameron.
不要自欺欺人 卡梅隆
-Fuck you. -You're dying.
-你去死吧 -你快要死了
You're dying.
你快要死了
-You're dying, Cam-- -Stop!
-你快要死了 卡梅… -闭嘴
Stop.
闭嘴
Jack was ready.
杰克准备好了
They're in good hands.
他们很安全
They're in your hands.
他们在你的保护之下
I wanna see the video.
我想看视频
Now.
马上
And you need to stop watching my family.
你必须停止监视我的家人
I learned that from school. Paper is wood.
我在学校里知道了纸是木头
Yes.
是的
-It's got some-- Let me see. -Is it?
-它有…让我看看 -是吗？
Some wood up there.
是有一些木头
Yeah. Yes, sir.
是 是的 先生
-This the only feed? -Okay.
-这是唯一的信号流吗？ -好的
Yes.
是
I'd like to be alone.
我想一个人待着
Nope.
不
So, what's one thing I've been trying to get you to do more of?
我想让你多做的一件事是什么？
-Read? -Good.
-阅读？ -很好
Here's a little something for you.
这里有一样小东西给你
Essentially, it's from your grandmother.
这其实来自你的祖母
It's something she gave to me when I was about your age.
我在你这个年龄的时候 她给了我
Open it up, it's a good one.
打开吧 很有意思的一本
Okay.
好吧
She wrote a little something in it.
她在里面写了点东西
I used to kill Andre for doing this to our books
我过去非常痛恨安德烈 在我们的书里面这样做
when we were growing up.
在我们小的时候
Now I'm, like, poring over every word he underlined.
现在我仔细研究他在下面划线的每一个字
Somehow I'm--
不知怎么地 我…
Somehow I'm finally breathing again.
不知怎么地 我终于可以呼吸了
But I feel like I've lost you, Cam.
可是我感觉失去了你 卡梅
You keep yourself so busy in a job you hate.
你在你讨厌的工作中忙忙碌碌
It's like you're not here.
就好像你不在这里
And I'm not saying you're fully to blame, you know? We're both in this.
我不是说这都怪你 你明白吗？我们都有错
I know I checked out for a while.
我知道我有段时间有些疏远
And I know that scared you.
我知道那让你害怕
And I'm sorry for that, Cam. I am.
我对此很抱歉 卡梅 真的
I mean, hearing you say the words, "I hit my head," the other day…
那天听到你说“我撞到了头”
I couldn't lose you, Cam. I couldn't live.
我不能失去你 卡梅 我没法活下去
So this is me telling you that I'm done with the silence now.
所以我这是在告诉你 我现在不想再沉默了
We start communicating, and we fix things.
我们开始沟通 我们解决问题
I made you a little something.
我给你做了一样东西
It's really insensitive.
这太不顾别人的感受了吧
Oh, no. I'm-- I'm sorry. I--
不 我…很抱歉 我…
Oh, shit. I'm so so--
见鬼 我很…
You little shit.
你这个鬼东西
You scared me.
你吓死我了
Your face. It's-- It's--
你的表情 太…
You scared me. That was good.
你吓坏我了 你真行
It is… It's good. Funny.
很…棒 真好笑
Hey, oh. It's okay.
嘿 没事的
You're okay.
你没事
I'm here. You're okay.
我在这里 你没事
He's taking out the contacts more and more,
他越来越频繁地摘下隐形眼镜了
not just when he goes to bed.
不仅是睡觉的时候
He doesn't have to wear them all the time. They make him feel uncomfortable.
他不必每时每刻都戴着 它们让他感觉不舒服
He feels badly for you.
他为你感到难过
But he also feels uncomfortable having his family watched.
但他也对别人监视他的家人感到不舒服
I don't give a shit about his comfort. That's my family.
我才不在乎他的不舒服 那是我的家人
What you're feeling right now, Cameron, is normal.
你现在的感受很正常 卡梅隆
No, it is not.
不 不正常
Something is wrong.
有什么事不对劲
For the last couple of days, I feel it. Something is off.
在过去两天中 我能感觉到 有什么不对劲
At this stage,
在这个阶段
whatever you're going through, it's normal. He's fine.
无论你在经历什么 感受都是正常的 他很好
Yeah.
好吧
What's up with you?
你是怎么回事？
Cory, it's time to eat, buddy.
科里 该吃饭了 伙计
Cory. Pause it.
科里 暂停它
Cory, come on.
科里 快点
What do you think?
你觉得怎么样？
I like it.
我喜欢
-Pecorino instead of Parmesan. -So good.
-用佩科里诺芝士代替帕马森芝士 -太好吃了
Yeah.
是的
Come on, man. Now. Pause it.
快点 伙计 立刻 暂停它
Less salty, right? Kind of sweeter?
没有那么咸 对吗？稍甜一些？
Yeah. It's great.
对 很棒
-You okay, babe? -Yeah, I'm fine.
-你没事吧 宝贝？ -我没事
-What's up? -No. I'm good. I'm good.
-怎么了？ -不 我很好…我只是…
You need to stop!
你给我停下
Oh, no.
不
Access denied.
拒绝访问
-Yeah. The waddle dance. -I'm gonna be a big brother!
-好棒 摇摆舞 -我要当哥哥了
-Good job! -We got the waddle dance.
-好样的 -我们在跳摇摆舞
I love him.
我爱他
Wow.
哇
Do what you need to do.
做你需要做的事
Hey, hey. Just, um…
嘿…
Just be careful.
小心一点
Hey, Doc.
嘿 小博士
Doc.
小博士
Wake up.
醒来吧
What's wrong?
怎么了？
I just had a really bad nightmare, and I just wanted to see you.
我刚做了一个噩梦 就是想看见你
Hey, I have an idea.
嘿 我有个主意
We're going to pretend that this is beer, okay?
我们假装这是啤酒 好吗？
My first was with my mom. I was a lot older than you, though.
我第一次喝啤酒是和我妈妈 不过我年龄比你大多了
But it's okay. We won't tell anybody.
不过没关系 我们不会告诉别人
Yeah.
好
And these guys were her favorite thing to eat with beer.
她最喜欢一边喝啤酒一边吃这些
Edamame with loads of salt.
很咸的毛豆
Washed down with a nice, crisp brew.
就着清爽的啤酒
-Yum. -How do you eat it?
-味道好极了 -这怎么吃？
See? Just grab the top one. Start one at a time with the top one.
瞧？捏住上面这个 从最上面开始一个一个吃
Pop it out. Yeah, go ahead. Yeah.
把它挤出来 对 来吧 对
-Tastes good. -Good, right?
-好吃 -不错 是吧？
Better than they look.
比看起来好吃
Yeah, now try it with your beer.
对 现在和你的啤酒一起吃
Okay.
好吧
Apple juice, but-- Hold up, hold on. Cheers.
是苹果汁 不过…等等…干杯
Long life for you.
长命百岁
To edamame.
为毛豆干杯
I'll just take one more.
我再吃一个
Come here, man.
过来 伙计
You okay, Dad?
爸爸 你没事吧？
Let me look at you, man. Let me look at that face.
让我看看你 伙计 让我看看这张脸
Yeah, I'm okay.
对 我没事
I'm okay.
我没事
Cory?
科里
Yes?
什么事？
I love you, man.
我爱你 伙计
I love you too, Dad.
我也爱你 爸爸
I know.
我知道
Be good, Doc.
乖乖的 小博士
P?
波？
P.
波
I love you.
我爱你
Poppy, wake up.
波比 醒醒
Bear, what's wrong?
熊熊 怎么了？
What's wrong?
你怎么了？
It's nothing. I just--
没什么 我刚…
I just had a really bad dream.
我刚做了个噩梦
I got angry at Cory. Dreamt I lost everything.
我生了科里的气 梦到我失去了一切
Oh, baby.
宝贝
Come here.
过来
God, you're shaking, sweetheart. You're shaking.
天啊 你在发抖 宝贝 你在发抖
It felt so real.
感觉太真实了
Oh, sweetheart.
宝贝
-We're here. Yeah? -Yes.
-我们在这里 对吗？ -是
We're doing better now. Yeah?
我们现在好多了 对吗？
Yeah, we're doing great.
对 我们很好
If it's a boy…
如果是男孩…
we should name him Andre.
我们应该给他起名叫安德烈
Yeah. I know.
是 我知道
Poppy?
波比
Yeah?
嗯？
I drifted.
我出过轨
Cam, stop it. Come here.
卡梅 别说了 过来
I'm so sorry. I just--
我很抱歉 我…
Listen.
听着
We're back, yeah?
我们合好了 对吗？
And it's wonderful.
这很棒
Yeah?
是吗？
Yeah.
是
Come here.
过来
Come on, get to sleep.
来吧 快睡吧
Thank you.
谢谢
Take care of 'em.
照顾好他们
I will.
我会的
As of this morning, he's officially Cameron Turner.
今天早上 他正式成为卡梅隆特纳了
He'll never know about any of this.
他将永远不会知道这些
Good.
很好
Thank you, Doc.
谢谢你 医生
Thank you.
谢谢你
It's hard to be left behind.
被人遗忘是很痛苦的
The new client is about to arrive.
新客户快要到了
Come down to us when you're done speaking with him.
等你跟他谈完后 到下面来找我们
Jack left you something.
杰克给你留了样东西
Babe?
宝贝
Tell me you love me.
告诉我你爱我
I love you.
我爱你
No, no, no.
不…
Cam.
卡梅
What are you doing? I'm chopping stuff.
你在做什么？我在切菜
For real, P.
说真的 波
What?
怎么了？
Look me in the eyes and tell me you love me.
看着我的眼睛 告诉我你爱我
-What are you doing? -Just-- Come on. For real.
-你在做什么呀？ -过来 真的
I need to hear it.
我需要听你说
Okay.
好吧
I love you, Cameron Turner.
我爱你 卡梅隆特纳
Always have. And always will.
一直是 永远都是
-How was that? -That was good.
-怎么样？ -太棒了